

Contact



+98 921 635 1266



Tehran, Iran



morteza-karimi.ir

me@morteza-karimi.ir



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi

Hard Skills

PHP Python JavaScript Yii2 Laravel React.JS

• • 000 $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$

••000

Node.JS **Tensorflow**

Vue.JS



Interests









Languages

Persian English



Morteza Karimi

Web Developer

About Me

I'm a flexible learner and detail oriented individual with valuable experience in different fields such as Web Developing, Deep learning, Networking...

As a boy with team work character, I always work side by side with team in all companies at which I have worked.

I extremely enjoy new experiences and challenges. In other word I prefer to follow new challenges instead of routine works. The quote "Either try as hard as you wish or wish as hard as you try" has been always my motto.

By the way reputation for hand-working, creativity, problem solving and team working are the highlights of my character.

Education

Shahrood University of Technology

2017 - Present

Master of Science in Artificial Intelligence; GPA: 3.77 (16.46/20)

Khayyam University of Mashhad

2012 - 2017

Bachelor of Engineering in Software Engineering; GPA: 3.17 (15.47/20)

Experience

Heyzha Programming Co

Web Application Developer

2017 - 2019

Cooperation with Heyzha company was a great spark for success in my work life. I did lots of project in this company. At first I started my work with solving the problems of a website with Laravel framework. Also I developed other websites with Yii2 framework and it followed a great impact because it caused 33% improvement in all the projects of Heyzha company. In the same way the income of company for developing more and more projects had improved, So the company experienced an up ward trend. By the way I experienced such a great challenges in designing complicated portals.

Khayyam University of Mashhad

Back-End Web developer

2014 - 2016

In Khayyam university I had a game project. Its name was tik-tak-toe that was in relation with IOS app. For developing it, I used node.js platform and socket.io library. Also I experience a team work project in this university. It was developing Khayyam university culture center website. Actually because of my good background in bachelor final project, use node.js and PHP together, this great project was given to me.



Contact

+98 921 635 1266



Tehran, Iran



morteza-karimi.ir



me@morteza-karimi.ir



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi

Hard Skills

PHP Python

JavaScript

Laravel

Yii2

• • 000

React.JS Vue.JS

 $\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$

Node.JS **Tensorflow**

••000 • • 0 0 0

OpenCV

••000

Interests









Languages

Persian



English



Freelance Experience

Full-Stack Web developer

2012 - Present

• Promac Co.

For the first time I used my admin panel in developing this website, so it followed a great impact and it was the satisfaction of employer.

• Rastegary charity website

It's one of my freelance works in the early years of my work field of web de-

I tried to use PHP MVC framework Yii And UI framework Bootstrap in this web project.

The first ideas of building my custom admin module for the next projects was occurred during developing this project that was very useful for my future projects.

• Variable project

I've done different kind of student projects that included website design and android application.

I worked with electron framework, Qt C++ framework, python language and many other techniques in these projects.

Volunteer Experience

Artificial Intelligence projects

Programmer

2017 - Present

Because of my intrest in Image Processing field, voluntary I worked on image processing projects.

Also based on my information about deep learning I started working on a project, that is about forecasting financial markets which is currently underway.

Create RTL template based on Gentelella theme

Front-End & Translate

2014 - Present

Sharing my abilities and information in translating and RTL on open source template was one of my great work experience.

By searching in google I found out a useful template so I worked on it because having good and free template could be useful for web developers.

I got familiar with different tools in this project and got many feedback from many people all around the world that helped me in developing this project.



Contact



+98 921 635 1266



Tehran, Iran



morteza-karimi.ir



me@morteza-karimi.ir



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi



MortezaKarimi

Hard Skills

PHP	
Python	
JavaScript	
Yii2	
Laravel	
React.JS	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$
Vue.JS	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$
Node.JS	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$
Tensorflow	••000

Interests

OpenCV







• • 0 0 0



Languages

Persian **English**









Valencia fan club website in Iran

Full-Stack Web developer 2014

I started my first work experience in field of "web developing" with designing 0 to 100 Valencia fan club website. I had a serious plan for developing this website that led to my employer satisfaction. I used Yii framework for this website to create complicated system such as like, comment and ... efficiently.

Web Development Teacher

Teacher

2014 - 2019

I always like to share my information with others so I like to have some experiences in designing open source projects or teaching my information to others. So I decided to schedule and plan some courses to teach web development lessons to my students.